我在哪儿
Where am I?
这是什么鬼地方
Where the fuck am I?
老天
Jesus.
洛根
Logan?
洛根 你在哪儿
Logan, where are you?
-洛根  -我操
- Logan! - Oh, fuck.
我在哪儿
Where am I?
没事的
It's OK.
我们在一个新地方
We're in the new place.
-对不起  -没事
- I'm sorry. - It's OK.
你说啥 老兄
What's that, man?
-我们到了 罗伊先生  -就是今天
- We're here, Mr. Roy. - This is it.
今天就是我们创造历史的日子 费克雷
This is the day we make it happen, Fikret.
您是天选之人 罗伊先生
You're the man, Mr. Roy.
祝您成功
You're the man.
可以了吗
We good?
我的天
Jesus Christ.
伙计们
Hey, hey, hey, buddy.
真高兴见到你
Good to see you.
咱们准备好大干一场了吗
So, are we ready to fuck or what?
好... 好吧
Yeah... OK.
我说 真的很遗憾
Look, I-I'm really sorry,
似乎出了点问题
but it looks like there's an issue.
拜托 我这么大老远都来了 哥们
Come on, I came all the way up here, dude.
很遗憾...
Yeah, I'm sorry...
哥们
Uh, dude.
好吧
OK.
听着 你知道我喜欢你做的事 对吧
Listen, you know I love what you do, right?
我很想让你和你的团队继续做下去 劳伦斯
I'd love to keep you and your team in place, Lawrence.
沃尔特烂得像屎
I think Vaulter is the shiz.
我们很烂吗
We're the shiz?
对
Yeah.
还有什么条件
What's it gonna take?
就算要我今天往你家运一台古董捷豹
You want me to send a vintage Jaguar over to your house today?
我也会照做
I'll do it.
我明白 但是...
Um, s-sure. Look, um...
就底价而言
I just think bottom line,
我要为自家股东们创造更大的价值
I can deliver a lot more value for our shareholders.
希望这不会对你造成困扰
I hope we haven't inconvenienced you.
我算明白了
I see you. I see this.
谢谢贵司对我们小团队的认可
We appreciate your interest in our little outfit,
但到此为止吧
but I think that's it.
别这样 到此为止吗
Come on. That's it?
不能这样结束 搞毛线呢
That's not it. What the fuck happened?
等一下
Yo, hang on.
慢着 慢着
Hold up, hold up.
-你收到消息了吗  -什么
- You get the message? - What?
我不会让你们这些穴居人们掠夺我的公司
I'm not letting you Neanderthals in to rape my company.
永远不会
Ever.
什么
I'm sorry?
你们就是群傲慢的恐龙
You're a bunch of bloated dinosaurs
快饿死了才发现猴子就在眼皮底下跑
who didn't even notice the monkeys swinging by till yesterday.
总之 去你妈的 小屁孩
Well, fuck you, daddy's boy.
别这样 这事儿不能吹
Hey, come on. Don't blow this up.
我手里有一份销售记录
I got a track record from founding
来自世界上最新潮的媒体品牌之一
one of the most exciting new media brands in the world.
你有什么
And what do you got?
射击废物留下的痕迹吗
Track marks from shooting junk?
谢谢你来 很高兴见到你
Thanks for coming down. It was great to meet you.
但这事儿谈不成的
Sorry this isn't going to work out.
不 可以的
No, it's gonna work out.
不 真的不行
No, it isn't.
保重 哥们
Take care, dude.
操 这他妈怎么回事 弗兰克
Fuck. What the fuck, Frank?
-我...  -我们该怎么补救
- I...  - How can we salvage this?
你还想谈这单吗
You still want to pursue this?
废话 我当然想继续谈
Yeah, of course I wanna pursue.
还要开发布会
I wanna announce.
这是计划的一部分
This is part of the whole thing.
是秘密武器
This is the secret sauce.
我们要给个更诱人的出价吗
Do we need to sweeten the offer?
你想把出价再提高一个点吗
You wanna bump the offer another point?
要给你爸打电话吗
Do you wanna call your dad?
要给我爸打电话吗
Do I wanna call my dad?
不 我不想给我爸打电话
No, I don't wanna call my dad.
你要给你爸打一个吗
Do you wanna call your dad?
-不  -不用吗
- No. - No?
你要打吗
Do you wanna call your dad?
还有人要给老爸打电话的吗
Does anybody wanna call their dad?
行 没人想他妈跟自己老爸讲话
OK, nobody wants to talk to their fucking dad.
那么 既然开始了 就把那破公司买下来
So, we've started, so let's buy this fucking company.
把报价提到1.2亿 行吗
I'm pushing the bid to 120. OK?
可以
OK.
进行得如何
How's it going?
挺好的 还在努力 爸
Yeah, I'm right in the middle, Dad.
成功了吗
Did you close?
还算顺利
Yeah, it's OK.
但离成功还差一点
We're not quite closed.
我打算提到1.2亿
I'm going to 120.
所以 还行
So, that's good.
咱们还能办发布会吧
and are we still good for the announcement?
可以
Uh-huh.
那就好 因为显然我这边
Great, 'cause obviously I'm soft floating
还要软处理弗兰克和拉瓦
to, you know like, Frank and Rava,
而且有人在传播谣言
and there's gossip getting soft floated.
谁
By who?
就 网民吧
Uh, by the ether.
我也不知道
I don't know.
对了 生日快乐 怪老头
Hey, hey, happy birthday, you old geezer.
你看 这事儿激动人心
Look, it's exciting.
会对你有好处的 老爹
This is gonna be great for you, Dad.
我很激动
Mm-hmm. I'm excited.
韦斯达·罗伊科是个大家庭
Waystar Royco is a family.
这个家庭横跨四大洲
A family that spans four continents,
五十个国家 拥有三个部门:
50 countries, three divisions:
娱乐部 新闻部和度假区部
Entertainment, News and Resorts.
协同合作
Working together
共同编织成一张网络包罗世界
to provide a net that can hold the world,
推动世界向前
or catapult it forward
致下一段征程
to the next adventure!
加入韦斯达·罗伊科
Joining Waystar Royco, you're joining
就是加入世界上最具活力的
one of the most dynamic news and entertainment companies
新闻娱乐公司之一
in the world.
用心感受
Feel it!
好的 大家觉得怎么样
OK, how's everyone feeling?
-好极了  -很棒
- Great! - Great!
很好
Excellent!
你在听吗
Hey. You in the room?
好 那这就出去给孩子们留下
OK. Well, let's go out and give these kids
最美好难忘的回忆吧
the best day of their lives, huh?
用心感受
Feel it!
-用心感受  -用心感受
- Feel it! - Feel it!
你好
Hi!
你好 道德里克
Hi, Doderick!
你好啊
Hi!
早上好
Good morning!
是道德里克
It's Doderick!
是我呢 我就是道德里克
Whoo! It's me, Doderick!
生日快乐
Hey, happy birthday!
别拽我的尾巴
Don't pull on my tail!
别打道德里克
Don't hit Doderick!
喂
Hey!
住手
Quit it!
等一下 行吗 请下去
Wait, OK. Please get off.
能滚下去吗
Can you fuck off?
给我滚下去
Can you just get the fuck off?
呕
Ew!
他的眼睛在呕吐
He's puking out of his eyes!
蛋白质泄露而已
Protein spill.
过来 过来 往这边来
OK, this way, this way. Come on.
格雷格
Greg?
妈妈
Hi, Mom.
你... 还好吗 工作怎么样了
How... Are you OK? How's it going?
妈 对不起 我好像闯祸了
Mom, sorry, but I sort of screwed up.
其实不是我 而是那小孩
Well, not me, actually, but this kid.
格雷格
Greg.
有个小孩在我车里抽了一根大麻
So, this kid smoked a joint in my car.
小孩
A kid.
就今早我接上的那个
Like this hitchhiker kid that I
搭便车的小孩 早些时候那会儿
picked up this morning, like earlier this morning.
因为那时在下雨 我不想...
'Cause it was raining and I didn't want...
不想他被坏人性骚扰之类的
I didn't want him to get sexually assaulted?
格雷格
Greg.
我还没说啥呢...
Before I could even say anything...
你搞毛呢
What the fuck?
他上车就点了一根...
Aggressively takes out...
就是你知不知道 那种 大麻烟
Have you ever seen, like, so, a doobie?
车里都是焦臭的大麻味儿
And the car smelled like skunk weed.
我身上也是那味
And then I guess I smelled like it.
他们就说
And then they were just like,
"收拾东西滚蛋"
"Get all your stuff and go. "
格雷格
Greg.
你有没有想过告诉他们
Did you even think for one second
你是谁
to tell them who you are?
没有 我觉得...
No, I thought...
我不想当个混蛋
I didn't wanna be an asshole
也不想掺和进去
or get into it all.
-好吧  -我也不知道
- OK. - I don't know.
你接下来这样做
Here's what you're gonna do.
买张去纽约的机票
You're gonna get a plane ticket to New York.
是你伯伯...
It's your Uncle...
大伯父洛根要过生日
Your Great-Uncle Logan's birthday,
要办一个大型生日宴会
and they're having a big party.
我会打给玛西娅说你要去
I'll call Marcia and tell her you're coming.
他要过生日吗
It's his birthday?
你去参加派对
You're gonna go to the party.
再送一份体面的礼物
You're gonna get him a nice gift.
还要看着英俊潇洒
And you're gonna look nice.
穿上成年人的衬衫和西装
In a grown-up shirt and a grown-up blazer.
西装
A blazer?
我告诉你怎么做
I'll let you know.
不给出一个大数目他们是不会让步的
They're not gonna budge unless it gets to be a stupid number.
多大算大
What's a stupid number?
多大 数兆亿吗 谁知道
What's stupid? A "badillion"? I don't know.
因为1.2亿够大了 不是吗
Because 120 is stupid. Am I wrong?
1.2亿是个大数目
120 is a stupid number.
这已经不是钱的事情了
But it's not really a money thing right now.
罗伊先生 有人找您
Mr. Roy, someone's here to see you.
-好 谁找我  -打扰 是肯德尔·罗伊吗
- OK. Who's this? - Hi, Kendall Roy?
是我 你好
Yeah, hi.
罗曼派我来烧点鼠尾草
I was sent by Roman to burn some sage.
你说什么
Excuse me?
求个好彩头
It's auspicious.
我是个商业炼金师
I'm a business alchemist.
这是你弟送你的礼物
It's a gift, from your brother.
会触发烟雾报警器吗
Will it set off the smoke alarms?
通常不会
Not usually.
啥叫通常
Not usually?
嘿 混蛋们
Hey, hey, motherfuckers!
-罗曼  -我的人吗
- Roman. - My guy?
开始烧了吗
Are you saging?
我们担心这会触发警报
Well, we're concerned about the alarms.
说得是啊 巫术
Ooh, right, yeah, the bad juju.
我可以用精油代替
Now, I can use essential oils.
你可以滚蛋了 谢谢
Oh, I think just fuck off, thanks.
你最近咋样
How ya doing?
不错 我们正在商议对策
Good. Good. Just finessing.
商议对策 很好
Mm. Finessing. Nice.
再见
Bye.
他很不错
He's good.
你没事吧
You OK, man?
我吗 好啊 好得不行了
OK? Yes, I'm OK. Obviously.
这还用问吗
Why would you even ask that?
不知道 问问而已
I don't know. Just, you know.
回来吗 早就翻篇了 我不适合这里
Here? Man, I'm so over it. I was a bad fit.
我从来不是拍企业主马屁的料
I was never a corporate cock-suck anyway.
更何况 我在这栋楼里从来没有爬到这么高
Besides, I never made it this high in the fucking building!
他们把我丢在洛杉矶混日子
They stuck me in LA with Old Father Time right here.
咱们以前是泳池兄弟 对吗 弗兰克
We were the pool boys, right, Frank?
记得香蕉小屋吗
Fuckin' banana cabana?
都是美好时光
Good times.
目前竞价是多少
So, what's the bid?
-你问竞价吗  -对
- What's the bid? - Mm-hmm.
这个...
Well...
怎么 这还算商业机密了
What? That's commercially sensitive?
我可还在董事会呢 兄弟
I'm still on the board, man.
要到1.25亿了
Going 125.
1.25亿吗
One-twenty-five?
-怎么了  -我去
- What? - Fuck!
怎么 高了还是低了
What? High or low?
-你笑什么  -没什么
- You're laughing. What? - No.
-为了买沃尔特 对吗  -是啊
- For Vaulter, right? - Yeah.
那个没啥内涵的商标吗
Bit of content and a brand name?
没啥内涵的商标就是精髓
Bit of content and a brand name kinda's the whole game.
-不是吗  -好吧
- Isn't it? - Mm-hmm.
你到底在笑什么？
What are you laughing at?
我不知道我在说什么
I don't know what I'm talking about.
反正你马上要当这艘船的船长了
You're gonna be captain of the ship soon enough.
-我不...  -嘘
- So I don't... - Shh.
糟糕
Oh, shit.
抱歉 去你妈的
Sorry. Fuck you, man.
街上的所有实习生都知道你要上位了
Every intern on the street knows that you're stepping up.
恭喜你 真心的
Seriously, congrats.
能离开这里我实在太高兴了
I'm just so pleased to be out of here.
这里对我简直就像个牢笼
This place was essentially a cage to me.
我该走了 管他妈的
I should take off. Fuck it.
恭喜你 兄弟
Hey, congrats, man.
谢谢你过来
Thanks for coming by.
瞧这胡诌八扯的地方
Look at all this fuckin' bullshit!
我很严肃的哦
Mm, yes, mm, very serious, mm.
爱你哦 老哥
Love you, brother.
很好
Good.
好
Right.
把它们都摆正 明白吗
Just keep everything straight, OK?
很好
Good.
对了 还要加一套新餐具
By the way, we need another setting.
还有一位家庭成员要来
Another family member is coming.
-玛西  -怎么了
- Marcy. - What?
我要出去 定好了的
I'm heading out, as ordered.
好的 一点前回来...
Great. Till 1:00...
好吧 但惊喜就在这里 好吗
Fine. But in here, yeah?
我他妈可不想被吓出心脏病
I don't want a fuckin' heart attack from the surprise.
我出电梯时 不想看到任何人朝我欢呼
And I don't want anyone in my face when I come out of the elevator.
保持好距离
Right. Distance.
把他们安排在这 还有...
Have them here. And, uh...
-怎么了  -小点声
- What? - Not too loud.
你希望我把惊喜的精准细节发给你吗
Do you want me to email you the exact details of the surprise?
想吗
Yeah?
-待会儿见  -好
- I'll see you later. - Yeah.
还有 穿好外套
Right. Get your coat.
知道了
Yeah, yeah.
理查德 把外套递给他
Richard, get him his coat.
好的
Of course.
-再仔细检查一遍  -好的
- Just double-check. - OK.
你打算多久去审演讲稿
When were you gonna look at that speech?
我周日晚上回来 到时候和他一起审 行吗
I'll be back by Sunday night so I'll look at his speech with him then, OK?
但他那边要在前周末拿到民调数据
OK, but his office wants the poll numbers by the preekend.
"前周末" 这他妈是啥玩意儿
The "preekend"? What the fuck's a "preekend"?
前周末就是周五
Preekend is Friday.
那他不能直接说是周五吗
If he wants them by Friday, can he not say Friday?
前周末是周四午后到周五中午
Thursday lunch through Friday afternoon is the preekend.
好吧 让蕾妮搞好数据
Oh, fine. Get Rennie to look at the numbers.
小西
Shiv.
真他妈是场灾难
This is a fuckin' disaster.
我得好好挑礼物
I got to strategize my gift.
他会喜欢什么礼物呢
What can I get him he'll love?
不清楚 我爸没什么喜好的
I don't know. My dad doesn't really like things.
他没什么喜好吗
He doesn't like things?
确实是这样
No, not really.
这份礼物要表达出
It needs to say that "I respect you,
"我尊重你 但我并不怕你
but I'm not awed by you.
我还... 欣赏你
And that I... I like you,
但我要你在我爱你之前 欣赏我"
but I need you to like me before I can love you."
所以选啥礼物好
So what says that?
听着 你买任何东西给他
Just, look, everything that you get him
都相当于没买
will mean an equal amount of nothing,
只要看上去价值一万到一万五就可以了
so make sure it looks like 10 to 15 grand's worth and you're good.
你能进来帮帮我吗
Will you come in here and help me?
好
Yes.
求你帮帮我
Please help me.
当然了 给他买块表吧
Yes. Get him a watch.
要是我们连股票也送
If we go stupid on the stock,
这份诱人的福利礼包看着如何
what does a really sexy package look like? Hmm?
他也许没有流动资金了 对吗
He's probably illiquid, right?
那我们要再投一千万吗
So, what, we throw in another ten million?
没准还要再来一次跪舔
Might need to throw in a blow job, too.
我来跪舔
I'll throw in a blow job.
还要让他高潮
I'll throw in a reach-around.
见鬼 我还要捏他的蛋
Hell, I'll even cup his balls.
爸
Dad.
你这会儿该到圣巴特岛[加勒比度假岛]了啊
I thought you'd be in St. Barts by now.
-一切顺利吗  -还不错
- How's it goin'? - Good.
是的 挺好的
Uh, yeah. Fine. Good.
你怎么...
Uh, why are you...
我们没事吧
Are we OK?
当然 就是些文件而已
Yeah, it's just some paperwork.
怎么 发布会前还有吗
What, ahead of the announcement?
我要把玛西纳为信托人... 破事一桩
Putting Marcy on the trust. It's... bullshit.
然后就想顺路过来瞧瞧
I, uh, I just felt like checkin' in.
是吗 好啊
Oh. Yeah, fine.
-只是改信托人吗  -对
- So this is just the trust? - Yeah.
不会阻碍我升职吧
Doesn't affect me stepping up?
不 不 不会的 我好像跟你谈过了
No, no, no, no, no. I think I told you about it.
这是...
Is that...
抱歉 父亲 我这边正忙...
Sorry, Dad, I'm kind of in the middle of...
你需要... 需要我走法律形式吗
Do you need... Do I need to lawyer all this?
一些家务而已
It's housekeeping.
好吧 我对玛西没意见
Fine. Yeah. Yeah. Marcy's fine by me.
我是说 那几个家伙可能不这么想 但...
I mean, the others might not feel the same, but...
我会处理的
I'll deal with that.
那我们...
So, I'll see you in...
对了 爸 午饭这事
Yeah, look, Dad, on lunch.
我很想陪你的 但是生意...
I really want to be with you, but the deal...
-儿子  -你知道的
- Son. - You know.
你自己决定吧
It's your call.
分清主次
Just priorities.
这种事以后只会更多
There'll be plenty more.
麦穗的故事 记得吗
Uh-oh. Wheat.
再见 弗兰克
Bye, Frank.
再见 老朋友
All right, amigo.
我有五个农场 而这些农场下面
I have five farms, and underneath all my farms
有个非常大的蓄水池 像地下湖那种
runs a big, giant aquifer that's like an underground lake.
-真酷啊  -我有抽水权
- That's so cool! - I have pumping rights.
就是说我能拥有那些水
That means I get to take the water.
-太酷了  -还相当重要呢
- That's so cool! - And it's very important
因为有一天 水会比黄金还珍贵
because someday water's gonna be more precious than gold
人们会互相残杀 只为得到水
and people are gonna kill each other to try to get that water.
悠着点 康纳 别这样
Oh, hey, hey, Con, don't, don't.
-别听他的  -我知道 抱歉
- Don't listen to him. - Right, right, sorry.
但我会拿到水的
But I'm gonna have the water.
然后就分享给你
And I'll share with you.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.
-你怎么样  -不错啊
- How are you? - Good.
-你呢  -很好 你看起来棒呆了
- How are you? - Good. You look great.
-颜色真漂亮  -谢谢 你的也很美
- What a beautiful color. - Thanks. Same.
-谢谢  -我很喜欢
- Thank you. - Love that.
谢谢
Thanks.
-汤姆  -玛西娅 最近好吗
- Hi, Tom. - Hey, Marcia, how are you?
-真高兴见到你  -我也很高兴见到你
- Nice to see you. - Nice to see you.
-你怎么样  -非常好
- How are you? - Very good.
环球汤姆 你还好吗
Hey, Global Tom. How you shaking?
还在为我们搞事吗
You still fucking shit up for us?
还在收拾你的烂摊子 伙计
Still cleaning up your mess, pal.
是啊
Yeah, right.
-你好啊 老妹  -好啊
- Hey, sis. - Hi.
政治还让你无聊到死吗
Politics still boring the living shit out of you?
当然 就埋埋尸体 数数钞票罢了
Yeah, you know, I'm burying the bodies, counting the cash.
瞧瞧你 还挺像个活人的
Look at you. You like, you know, an actual human person.
谢了 老哥
Well, thanks, buddy.
-好  -这什么味儿
- Hi.  - Oh, what is that?
CK的"约会强奸"吗
Date Rape by Calvin Klein?
你想得美
Yeah, you wish.
"你想得美"
"You wish"?
-罗伊先生  -请您看这 罗伊先生
- Mr. Roy!  - Mr. Roy, please!
罗伊先生 看这里 就照一张
Mr. Roy. Over here. One shot, please.
伙计们 能不能退后
Say, guys, can we back off?
-笑一个怎么样  -伙计们 退后 这是私人活动
- How 'bout a smile? - Guys, back off. Private event.
洛根 洛根 今天您要出席 对吗 是吗
Logan, Logan, you going today? Is that right? Is that right?
-请退后  -滚边儿去
- Back off, please. - Fuck off.
-搞定他们 行不  -照一张就好
- Handle that, will ya?  - Just one shot!
罗伊先生
Mr. Roy.
你好 你好啊
Hi. Hello. Hello there.
需要帮助吗 先生
Can I help you, sir?
是的 我... 其实我是来找你的
Yeah, I'm actually... I'm actually here to see you.
把手放背后
Get your hands back!
你是谁
Who are you?
-你要做什么  -格雷格 我叫格雷格
- What are you doing? - Greg! I'm Greg!
我是玛丽安家的格雷格 我妈是你外甥女
I'm Marianne's Greg. Your nephew?
-你认识这人吗  -我妈给玛西娅打了电话
- You know this guy?  - My Mom called Marcia
我和那人说了 他说我可以上去
and I talked to that guy and he said that I could go up.
-没事了吗  -对
- We're good? - Right.
我不知道你要来
I didn't know you were coming.
-你知道吧  -刚才抱歉了 伙计
- Yeah, you did. - Sorry about that, guy.
-我觉得你应该知道  -你还好吧
- I think you did. - You all right?
-不好意思了  -希望没事
- Sorry about that. - I hope it's OK.
我想跟你说生日快...
I wanted to say happy birth...
祝你生日快乐 长命百岁
Happy birthday and many happy returns.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
跟我一起上楼吧
I suppose you better come up.
他是个尽职尽责的保镖
He's a very good bodyguard.
各位 他回来了
Folks, he's back!
他要到了 藏起来给他个惊喜 快
He's back. Find a place. Hide for the surprise. Come on.
我们真要给他个惊喜吗
Oh, we're not surprising him, are we?
-没错  -他肯定"爱死了"
- Yeah.  - Oh, he's gonna love this.
上次我给他一个惊喜
Think last time I surprised him,
他回我一记重拳
he took a swing at me.
你可能已经知道了 我得到过您的帮助
You might know this, but I got a little bit of help,
我参加了管培生的国际项目
and I got onto the international management training program?
在主题公园实习
The theme park tour?
我也算很投入
And I was very into it?
可是... 那天我病了
And... I got sick.
吐了布偶狗一眼睛
Out of Doderick's eyeholes.
生日惊喜
Surprise!
好 很棒 太妙了
Great. Excellent. Wonderful.
出去 出去
Go ahead. Go ahead.
你们好
Hi. Hi.
行了 行了 腾个地方 腾个地方
OK. OK. Give me room. Give me room.
谢谢 谢谢 真是惊喜啊
Thank you. Thank you. What a surprise.
-玛西娅  -怎么
- Marcia. - What?
我怎么嘱咐你的 我说了不要等在电梯口
What did I say? I said nobody by the elevator.
结果呢 每个人都等在电梯口
And what do I find? Everybody's by the elevator.
-是个惊喜啊  -真"惊喜"
- It's a surprise. - Oh, a surprise.
给我吧
Give me that.
请送到办公室去
In the office, please.
康纳 老大 你好吗
Connor, Primo! How are you?
不错 很棒 老爸 送给你
Good. Excellent, Pa. Here you go.
罗曼 罗慕路斯
Roman! Romulus!
瞧瞧你 看起来棒极了
Look at you! You look fantastic!
那是自然
Yeah, of course.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
西沃恩 亲爱的
Siobhan. Sweetheart.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
汤姆呢
Where's Tom?
他在这 就在这
He's here. He's just there.
好吧 当我没问
Oh, well, never mind.
各位 顺带一提 这位是... 克雷格
Everybody, this is... Craig, by the way.
克雷格表弟
Cousin Craig.
"克雷格" 是格雷格吧 不是吗
"Craig"? It's Greg. N-No?
是 是格雷格
Yeah. Greg.
人们有时会叫错 叫成克雷格
People sometimes, like, mistakenly call me Craig, too,
所以叫哪个我都应
so I'll answer to both.
这是我的一点心意
Here. This is just a token of my very
想表达我对您的真挚崇敬...
real and enduring admiration, in the hope...
肯德尔
Kendall?
你来了
You came?
是的 当然
Yeah, of course.
生日快乐 爸
Happy birthday, Dad.
-你好 玛西  -你好
- Hey, Marcy.- Hi.
-你好吗  -大喜的日子
- How are you?- Big day.
恭喜了... 你这混球
Congratulations... you bastard.
-祝贺你 祝你好运  -谢了
- Congratulations. Good luck.- Thanks.
你好 肯德尔
Hey. Hey, Kendall.
-过得如何  -有什么新消息吗
- How's it goin'?  - So! What's the news?
一切顺利 只差临门一脚
Yeah, good, good. We're at the one-yard line.
我得接一下... 这很重要
I'm just gonna... This is important.
抱歉了 各位 我很快回来
Uh, sorry, guys, I'll be right back.
抱歉 你好
Excuse me. Hello.
我听说你遇到麻烦了 真的吗
I hear you went down? Did you go down?
是啊 没错
Oh, yeah, I did.
很糟糕
Not so good.
一团糟
It's a shitshow.
我找个安静的地方
Just gotta get somewhere quiet.
我有新消息
Yeah, I got news.
快说
Hey, talk to me.
PPG银行闻风而动
Yeah, PPG Bank have got their nose in,
可能有别家参与竞标
might be rustling up another bid.
已经传开了 咱们得行动了 你想怎么办
Word's out. We gotta move. What do you wanna do?
五分钟后打给你
I'm gonna call you back in five.
-这笔交易我志在必得  -好吧
- I'm not losing this deal.  - All right.
联系PPG 我们可以在融资上给他们让利
We call PPG, we offer to cut them in on the financing
只要他们把另一家干掉
if they make the other bid fuck off.
好主意 肯 好主意
Great idea, Ken, great idea.
砰 肯德尔掌权 砰 搞定收购
Boom. Kendall takes over. Boom. Acquisition.
干净利落
That's how it's done.
我想跟你谈谈汤姆的事
Hey, you know, I wanted to talk to you about Tom.
他差不多准备好接手主题公园了
He thinks he might be ready for the parks,
-全球业务啥的...  -老爸
- you know, globally and...  - Look, Dad,
我们该聊点轻松愉快的话题
we should get this somewhere ambient.
-意下如何  -康纳 你好吗
- You want to?  - Connor. How are you?
-牧场怎么样  -完美
- How's the ranch?  - Oh, perfect.
那里基本不存在光污染
The light pollution is practically zero,
所以 你懂的 很棒
so, you know, that's nice.
-给你  -真好
- Hey.  - Oh, wonderful.
这是什么
What is it?
-这是... -对 就是这个
- Well...  - Oh, yes, yes.
这是一个... 粘团
It's a... It's a goo.
就他妈是个粘团
It's a fucking goo?
很完美
It's perfect.
这是酸酵头
It's sourdough starter.
棒呆
Amazing.
我觉得你可能想做点儿面包啥的
I thought that you might like to make something.
很棒
Ah, great.
那啥 你不该打开 好吗
Yeah, OK, you shouldn't have opened it. OK?
算了吧 罢了
Never mind, forget it.
我就是突发奇想 以为你会喜欢
It was an idea. I thought you might like it.
喜欢 我喜欢
I do. I do.
我只是不知道这是啥几把玩意儿
I just don't know what the fuck it is.
是酸酵头
It's sourdough starter
不用酵母做面包... 是古法
to make bread without yeast... The old way.
原来如此 好吧
Oh. Oh, OK.
古法面包 谢谢你
Old bread. Thank you.
-这很棒 非常感谢  -客气
- It's very kind. Thank you very much - You bet.
和气点
Be nice.
事情怎么样了
How's it lookin'?
一切向好
Looking good.
我会随时向你汇报
I'll keep you posted.
我刚问了弗兰克 年底的节假日期间
I just checked with Frank, and the holidays mean
董事会成员可能到不齐
the board might be kinda hard to get together,
所以如果你方便 我定了四点开董事会
so if it's cool I've scheduled a call at 4:00?
到时我们可以宣布
Then we can issue the release?
你定了吗
You did?
是的 行吗
Yeah. Is that OK?
你忙
You go on.
我不去
I'm not going.
-来跟爸爸抱抱  -午安 爸爸
- Hey. Give Daddy a hug.  - Hi, Daddy.
抱歉 我们迟到了
Sorry we're late.
不 没有 完全没有 别担心
No, no, you're not even. Don't worry.
二十分钟内都不算晚
Twenty's the margin of error.
抱歉我这几天都没跟你们视频
Hey, sorry I haven't Skyped with you guys in a couple days.
我太忙了 你们还好吗
I've been super busy. You feel good?
-还不错  -很好
- I'm good.  - OK.
看到那边的艾拉了吗 你们的朋友艾拉
You see Isla up there? Your friend Isla?
你们要不要去跟她玩
You guys wanna go see her, maybe make a
给爷爷画张像当生日礼物
drawing for Grandpa for his birthday?
抱歉 稍等
Sorry, one second.
没关系
It's OK.
我收到你的信息了 没关系
I got your message. That's fine.
对 没错
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
这个档口事情太多
It's just as this all goes through,
接下来两周会忙疯的
next two weekends will be kinda crazy.
但只要尘埃落定 要是能...
But then once it's done, it would be great if...
不 没事的 好饭不怕晚
Yeah, no, it's fine. Bank the weekends, spend them later.
好的 我可以去找你
OK. I can come up to you.
如果你愿意 我们交接孩子的时候一起吃个饭
Maybe if you want, we could grab dinner for the hand-over?
呃 孩子要在我这两周吗...
Ugh. What, like two weekends? Um...
不行吗 难道你... 你不会是...
No? Are you... Is that not...
你在交往别的人吗
Are you seeing someone?
是的
Yeah.
没错
I am.
我只希望这次没人把可卡因洒在孩子们的平板电脑上
And I'm just hoping this one doesn't leave coke smeared all over the kids' iPads.
好吧 要求很合理
All right, that's fair.
-天呐  -那是三年前的事了 但...
- Oh, God.  - It was three years ago, but...
肯德尔 我逗你玩呢
Kendall, I'm fucking with you.
没事 没事的 没问题
It's OK, it's OK. You're good.
这是你大喜的日子 加冕日
This is a big day. Coronation day.
-对  -这是你应得的
- Yeah.  - Hey, you deserve this.
我说真的 你经历了这么多
Seriously. After everything.
各位 十分钟后开饭
Guys, lunch in ten.
听我说 趁着还没开饭 到起居室来 我有事要说
Listen, just two minutes before lunch in the sitting room.
孩子们 能给我两分钟吗
Kids. Can you give me two minutes.
有个演讲
Got a speech.
-洛根伯伯 我能...  -待会儿再说
- So, Uncle Logan, can I... - Not now.
不好意思 先生 先生 我需要您听我说
Sorry, sir. Sir, sir, just, I need your attention, please.
关于... 我之前所说的
About the... what I was talking about earlier,
管理培训计划
the management training program?
我需要回去继续参加培训
I need to get back in.
-你退出了吗  -是的
- You're out? - Yes.
出了点小问题 我跟我母亲说了
There was an issue, and I talked to my mom
她与我祖父提了一下 然后让我来找您
who talked to my grandfather and said that I can come to you
就能... 解决这个问题
and... and iron it out.
我愿意为兄弟两肋插刀
I'll do anything for my brother.
那... 那太好了
Oh, that's... that's nice.
我会拼尽全力...
And I'm gonna work 100%...
他只用求我就好
All he needs to do is just ask.
我的祖父吗
My grandfather?
我是说 您二位交集甚少
I mean, you two don't talk so much.
对吧
Right?
两肋插刀
Anything.
只要他来求我
Just get him to ask me.
操
Fuck!
-爸  -什么事
- Dad. - Yes.
你要说什么事
Yeah, what's the deal?
所以...
So...
假如我不幸去世 家族信托
On the family trust, which will decide the situation
将掌控家族大局
in the event of my unlikely demise,
我要让玛西取代我 和你们四个一道
I'm going to add Marcy to myself and you four.
是吗
Whoa. OK.
在我死后 我的位置要留给她
And my seat also to go to her on my death.
什么 等下 这就给了她双份投票权了
What? Wait, that gives her double voting weight.
没错 我这里有几份文件...
Uh-huh. So I've got some paperwork...
等等 啥
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What?
在你那啥之后玛西娅有两票...
So Marcia will have two votes when you...
-"假如"他...  -小罗 才不是假如
- "If" he...  - Well, no, Rome, it's not an if.
抱歉啊 要是我不想让他...
Well, excuse me if I don't want him to...
小罗 这不是他的真正意图
Well, it's not really what we want in this case, Rome.
肯德尔已经签字了 但如果我能让你们全员...
Kendall's already signed, but if I can get you all to...
两票 我觉得我当时应该是没注意到...
Two votes? I don't think I was aware of that when I...
混球 那你倒是读附属细则啊
Read the small print, asshole.
这看起来...
I mean, this looks...
我要跟我的律师谈谈 弄清各项内涵
I'm gonna have to talk to my lawyers, just for all the implications.
请便
Of course.
看清全局
Just to get the full picture.
当然 三思而后行
Sure, take a beat.
但听着 我喜欢那面包... 还是粘团...
But look, I love the bread... goo...
但这才正是我最想要的礼物
But this is the present I really want.
四点前决定 行吗
By 4:00, good?
还有 我已经和肯德尔提过了
Oh, also, I already mentioned to Kendall,
除唠唠叨叨之外 其他的事都考虑到了
despite the chatter and all things considered,
我会再坚持几年
I'm going to give it a couple of years.
做什么
As in?
我会继续主持大局
I'll stay in situ.
仍然担任主席 总裁 公司的一把手
As chairman, CEO, head of the firm.
爸 你... 说啥
Dad, wh... you... you what?
我才说完 我的儿
I just said, son,
还是说你一如既往地没听我说话
or were you not listening, as usual?
但我才是... 你不是... 什么
But I'm... You're not... What?
没啥大不了的 我要继续主持大局
It's no big deal. I'm staying on.
-细节好商量  -你没跟我说过
- We can discuss the details. - You didn't tell me.
咱们能对外公布你仍留在决策圈
We can announce you're in pole position,
未定事项啊 升职什么的
pending events, a move up or whatever.
-"未定事项"  -行 不说了 吃饭吧
- "Pending events"? - OK, come on, let's eat.
爸 等一下
Dad, wait.
我操
Oh, fuck!
我不知道你他妈有什么好笑的
I don't know what you're fucking laughing about!
我根本没笑 搞毛呢
I'm not even laughing. What?!
操 操他妈的
Fuck. What the fuck.
他不能就... 对吧
I mean, he can't just... Right?
公司的声誉都得被他玩坏
He's gonna blow the firm's credibility.
你们觉得他还撑得下去吗
Did he look OK to you?
得了 肯 这是爸典型的作风
Oh, come on! Ken, this is typical. It's Dad.
我不干了 总成吧
I'm out, OK?
不玩了
I'm not playing.
不管你仨如何决定 悉听尊便
Whatever you three decide, goes.
-拜拜了您哪  -康纳
- Goodbye. - Connor.
我拒绝在信托上玩玩闹闹
On the trust, I refuse to play.
我不想趟这浑水 我是清水 我流走还不行么
I don't want to engage. I'm water, I flow.
这根本站不住脚的 对吧
This doesn't stand, right?
我...
I...
还他娘的耸肩 耸你妹的肩啊
Oh, fucking shrug? You're fucking shrugging me?
你发短信呢是吧 哥们 你干什...
Are you texting? Dude, what are you...
说你呢
Hey, hey!
-你当长舌妇呢  -你他娘的那么认真干什么
- Are you telling? - Are you fucking serious?
-啥 你14岁小毛孩吗  -这件事绝不能外传
- What, are you 14? Private. - Hey, this stays in here.
-懂吗 这件事禁止外传  -我们都需要心理咨询 伙计
- OK? This is a lockdown. - We all need advice, man.
咨询 啥玩意儿 你要把两票
Advice? What? You're gonna give a double vote
交给一个权利控制狂吗
to a power-hungry maniac
这人他妈指不定能弄出什么幺蛾子
who will do fuck-knows-what with it
就因为她用她的大逼紧紧夹住了爸的屌
because she's got our dad's dick in some Super Max pussy grip
在他胡言乱语前给他灌了什么浆
and she's juicing him before he croaks?
大家伙 饭好了
Guys? Lunch is coming up.
抱歉 我不想这么严格的
Sorry, I don't mean to be strict.
让我们单独待会儿 好吗 谢谢
Can you give us a minute, please? Thank you.
所以说... 你阴了我一道
Hey. So... you fucked me.
我改主意了 肯德尔
I changed my mind, Kendall.
多久 多久改的
When? When, exactly.
因为我觉得你就是阴了我
'Cause it feels like you fucked me.
主要还是在我
It's me. It's mainly me.
但你... 三年前
But you... Three years ago,
你还在精神病院
you were still in the nuthouse.
疗养 爸 那叫疗养
Rehab, Dad. It's called rehab.
而且我已经痊愈了
And I'm in recovery.
都不是事
It's all good.
但我担心你会变软骨头
I'm just concerned you might be soft, as yet.
软骨头 你开玩笑吧
S-Soft? Are you kidding?
我他妈在上海待了一年
I did a fucking year in Shanghai.
我听说你任由网站公司那男的灭你士气
I hear you let the guy from the website trash-talk you
你还毫无还击之力
and you just let him come.
那不是网站
It's not a website.
我也只是想专业点
And I was being professional.
我听说谈判很失败 逆向冲突
I hear it played weak. Conflict averse.
我又不是卷进了什么"比谁屌大"的竞争
I wasn't about to get into a fucking big dick competition.
好吗
OK?
听说你向他低头了
I hear you bent for him.
什... 我什么
Wha... I what?
听说你低头求他 却反被搞了
I hear you bent for him and he fucked you.
其实并没有
Well, no, actually.
我知道你读了很多
I know that you've read a lot of books
关于商务管理的这样那样的书
about business management and this and that,
但你猜怎么着
but you know what?
怎么着
What?
有时候这就是一场比谁屌大的竞争
Sometimes it is a big dick competition.
行 所以就这样了吗
OK. OK. So that's it?
所以我本该冲他们大喊 但我没有
So I should have shouted at some guy, but I didn't.
于是你就撕毁了18个月的合作战略吗
So you've ripped up 18 months of corporate strategy?
你也别想染指信托改动
And you never lawyered the trust change.
我相信我父亲 这也能成了污点
I trusted my father. That's a black mark?
日积月累吧
It's an accumulation.
你离开了房间 谈生意的那间
You left the room. The deal.
来给我爸过他妈的生日
To come to my Dad's fucking birthday party
因为天知道你还能过几个生日
'cause we don't know how many more there'll be!
对不起
Sorry.
告诉我吧
So come on.
你要多久能准备好
When will you be ready?
下任
To step down?
我不知道
I don't know.
五年吧
Five?
五年
Five years?
十年吧
Ten?
十年 爸 开玩笑吧
Ten! Dad? Seriously!
这他妈是老子的公司
It's my fuckin' company.
没错 这他娘的是你的公司 但你猜怎么着
Yeah, it is your fucking company, and you know what?
你快要把它带到阴沟里了
You're running it into the fucking ground.
你一辈子都耗在了砸钱上...
You spend all your time on costs...
你的远见呢 你已经落后了
Where's the vision? You're off the beat.
增益呢 数据全面下降 无一幸免
Where's the growth? All our graphs go down. All of them.
所以你要把十亿砸进一个破袖珍网站吗
Is that why you're paying a billion dollars for a gay little website?
都他娘的说了不是网站
It is not a fucking website!
这是一个在线品牌及数字视频的组合产品
It's a portfolio of online brands and digital video content
如果你让我放手一搏 这也是能挽救
and it's part of an upstream investment strategy
我们公司的上游投资策略
to save us, if you'll just let me.
你想打我 是吧
Do you want to hit me, is that it?
对吧
Huh?
来呀
Go on.
你使出吃奶的劲儿来
Give it your best shot.
爸 别这样 你在干嘛
Dad, come on. What are you doing?
你他娘的要哭不成
Are you gonna fuckin' cry?
肯德尔 你他妈在哭鼻子吗
Kendall, are you fuckin' crying?
你知道局势已经漂浮不定了吗
You know, this has been floated already?
外面什么样的说法都有 总有人来找我证实
There's fucking paps outside. I'm getting asked for quotes.
操他们的
Fuck them.
是 当然 "操他们的"
Yeah, 'course, "fuck 'em."
牛 牛逼的媒体策略 爸
Great, great media strategy, Dad.
牛逼的商务策略
Great business strategy.
-时移事易...  -对对对
- The world is changing... - Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
万事万物都在变化
Yeah, everything changes.
我买工作室那会 它就快破产了
The studio was gonna tank when I bought it,
人人都想待在家里看录像
everyone was gonna stay home with video tapes.
但你猜怎么样 并不是 大家都想出门找乐子
But guess what? No! They wanna go out.
没人看什么电视网
No one was gonna watch Network,
除非你来点刺激的 他们就乐意看了
except you give it zing and they do.
创造你自己的现实吧
You make your own reality.
而一旦你成功了 显然
And once you've done it, apparently,
每个人的观点都他娘的这么显而易见
everybody's of the opinion it was all so fucking obvious.
开饭
Lunch!
快来 找好位置 坐下
Come on. Find your places. Sit.
请把座位图递给我一下
Please give me my seating plan.
我有点弄混了 不好意思
This is confusing. Sorry.
她喝多了 坐到了戈尔·维达尔的腿上
She was drunk and sitting in Gore Vidal's lap.
她很风趣
She's very funny.
-你妈妈特别风趣  -戈尔·维达尔是谁
- Your mom's very funny. - Who's Gore Vidal?
她就是那个 你知道 长发披肩 老是穿着那种衣服的那个
She's the one, you know, with the hair, and she usually wears the clothes?
-是的  -是的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
是啊 不 我记得你女儿
Yeah, no, I remember your daughter.
玛西 很好吃 谢谢你
Marcy. This was delicious. Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
今天的安排都很用心
The whole day. Really thoughtful.
都很棒
It's been great.
十分感谢
Thank you very much.
你个马屁精
You're a suck-up.
很开心能邀请你
I'm happy to have you.
"你太棒了 能投两票的妈妈"
"You are so swell, Double Vote Power Mom!"
你他妈给我滚
You know what? Fuck you.
打扰下 我说两句...
If you'll excuse me...
洛根·罗伊
Logan Roy.
八十年前的今天 他生于苏格兰的丹地
Born in Dundee, Scotland, 80 years ago today,
叔婶在魁北克把他抚养长大 叔叔有家印刷厂和几个广告牌
raised in Quebec by an uncle with a print shop and a few advertising billboards
婶婶养着一群牛
and an aunt with a herd of cattle.
洛根在过去的六十年中给自己拼出了一条路
Logan himself has made a decent way for himself these past 60 years.
建立起世界第五大传媒帝国
Fifth largest media conglomerate in the world.
他是首相的哥们儿 和总统们无话不谈
A pal to prime ministers, a truth teller to presidents.
他坚韧 他老谋深算
He's tough, he's wily,
但他总是信守诺言
but he's always true to his word.
我三十年前开始做他的法律顾问
I arrived to give him legal advice 30 years ago,
至今也没离开
and I never got out the door.
时至今日 我很骄傲与他为友
And since that day, I'm proud to call him a friend.
那么 举杯吧
So, let's raise a toast.
敬洛根·罗伊
Logan Roy.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们也该玩那个游戏了
So, I think it's time to play the game.
要玩那个游戏吗
We're playing the game?
没错 是的
Well, yes.
今天是我的生日 当然要玩
It's my birthday, so yes, we're playing the game.
我们必须玩那个游戏吗
Do we have to play the game?
那个游戏是什么
What's the game?
到底是什么
天不错 你还好吗 格雷格
Nice day! You OK, Greg?
还好 我不... 车里还有地方吗
Sure. I'm not... Is there room in there?
上车
Hop in.
有点挤 抱歉
I'm sorry if it's a crush.
没关系
It's fine.
我跟我祖父通了话
I was just talking to my grandpa.
他跟你说生日快乐
And he said happy birthday.
他说了吗
Did he?
好吧 理论上 他没说
Well, no, not technically,
但他知道你过生日
but he's aware it's your birthday.
但跟他通话后 我突然想到
But it occurred to me, talking to him,
他仍在控股公司有席位
that him having his seat on the holding company still,
这是历史遗留问题
from historically,
某种程度上讲 他不是最佳人选
now, that must be suboptimal, in some ways.
但如果我可以... 如果他愿意把这个位置
But if I could... if he was willing to give his seat
让更精明的人来接替
to someone a bit more perspicacious,
让更熟悉门道的人来运营这些主题公园
someone who could learn the ropes, running a theme park, say.
运营这些游乐场
Running the parks?
交给年轻人 不断学习
Just a little guy. Learning, you know?
那个人选...
I mean, could that be...?
你要是帮我 我...
You scratch my back, I...
虽说我并不能回报你什么
I'm not gonna say I could scratch yours.
因为这个范围太大了
It's be too considerable of a space.
但... 也许你能考虑下
But is there an angle there, perhaps?
儿子 你什么想法
So... what're you thinking, son?
对于这件事
On the thing?
她很聪明
She's very smart.
她是很好的人选 家人优先
She'd make good picks. Family first.
我懂 我懂的
I'm sure. I'm sure.
那你为什么不高兴
But what's your cut?
我没
Um... No.
没有 我天 爸我没不高兴 这是你的公司
No. God no, Dad. No, it's your firm.
这跟我没什么关系
Like, it's not what's in it for me.
不过 到底能不能有点关系
But you know, like, what is in it for me?
我倒是想让你回公司
I'd love to get you back in.
行 也行
Sure. No, sure.
可上回不怎么样
It's just it was tough last time.
弗兰克在洛杉矶管我太严了
It was very tough with Frank over me in LA.
弗兰克对公司很重要
Frank's very important to the firm.
可不是 很重要 当然 我理解
Oh, no, sure. No, of course, I understand that.
只不过 我在制片上有很多点子
It's just I had a lot of ideas at the studio.
你也知道 我是大创新思想家
As you know, I'm quite an innovative thinker,
可我遇到了很多阻力
and I was met with a lot of resistance.
这还是因为节目吗
Is this still the film thing?
不是... 你说机械奥运会吗
No... Oh, what, Robot Olympics?
不 爸 不只是这一个好点子
No, Dad, it's not about one fantastic idea.
这是种文化 当时有很多这种点子
It was a culture. There were many of them.
你想怎样呢
What would be your dream outfit?
我想做那节目的制片 非常想
I wanna run the damn show. I do.
运行起来以后 我要做首席运营官
And until it opens up, Chief Operating Officer.
但我猜... 位置应该是弗兰克的 对吧
But I guess... I guess that's Frank, huh?
你还好吗
You OK?
不错 你呢
Sure. You?
人都到了
The boys are here!
您这边走
Just right this way.
这是我第一次坐直升机
That was my first helicopter ride.
太疯狂了
It was so crazy.
比我想象的快多了
It goes so much faster than I thought.
见到你很高兴
Hey, it's good to see you.
好了 大家把手套戴好
OK, let's get a glove.
再给我倒点
Let's have a second.
几点了
What time is it?
-往这扔  -回来 回来
- Toss it over here! - Come on back, come on back.
目前局势有些动荡 你要回公司吗
Now that things are getting shaken up, would you come inside?
爸 我不是随便搞搞政治
Dad, I'm not just playing with the politics.
对 当然 政治
Oh, no, of course. Politics.
我不想说的太直白 但政治就是拉出来的屎
Not to be crude about it, but politics is what comes out the asshole.
明明回来有体面的工作 干嘛要去玩屎
Wouldn't you rather be up front, feeding the horse?
乔伊丝表现地像我已经入主白宫了
Well, Joyce, she's got that Air Force One look.
所以... 真要我回来帮忙 我必须万人之上
So... to come back, I'd want the top job.
但要是很难怎么办
And if that was difficult?
你要掌管所有海外的部分 游乐场等全部
Overseeing everything outside the US, parks and all.
什么... 你是说 做汤姆的老板
What, like... Tom's boss?
没错 垫脚石
Yeah. Stepping stones.
那来求救的小崽子到底要什么
What's the rescue pup looking for?
他搞砸了工作 需要帮助
He screwed up. Needs help.
他将来可能适合游乐场的管理
He might fit in eventually to the parks.
你觉得汤姆能处理好这种竞争吗
Do you think Tom can handle the competition?
罗伊先生 准备就绪
Mr. Roy. All set.
这就对了
There you go.
那啥
Hey.
我想把这个亲手交给您
So, just wanted to give this to you
当面跟您说声 生日快乐
in person just to say, you know, happy birthday.
帮我拿下
Hold that, will you?
是块百达翡丽表...
It's just a Patek Philippe. So...
我知道 写着呢 "百达翡丽"
Yeah, it says "Patek Philippe."
是 我知道
Yeah. I know.
这表极其准
It's incredibly accurate.
每次你看向它
Every time you look at it,
都能准确展示你的富有
it tells you exactly how rich you are.
这话挺逗的
That's very funny.
刚这段你彩排过吗
Did you rehearse that?
没 我没有 好吧 有 但是...
No. Well, no. Yes. But...
好 还行
OK. Yeah.
给
Here.
好了 开始玩球了
OK, let's play ball.
好了 你们怎么想
So, what are you thinking?
我想我们集体反对改信托人 一致对外
We say no, all of us, on the trust. Full block.
要稳定 得按原计划来
Stability. Stick to the plan.
我上位 之后我们只要...
I take over and we just...
你俩 在我之下 做两位总裁
You two, under me, co-presidents.
-在你之下  -没错
- Under you? - Uh-huh.
但是 你懂的 我们三人并肩作战
But, you know, three. The power of three?
有趣
Interesting.
-我们能想下吗  -当然
- Can we think about it? - Of course.
我想完了 滚你丫的
I thought about it. Fuck you.
上啊 拉瓦
Go, Rava!
看穿你了
Psych your mind!
上啊
Go!
好球
That's a strike.
-骗到她了  -球扔得不错
- Got her looking! - That's good pitching.
-换边  -老兄
- Change sides! - Hey, man.
跟跳芭蕾一样
It was balletic, though,
感觉出来了...
kinda came around..
听说你是新成员 对吗
I hear you're the new kid. Yeah?
对 我才刚开始...
Oh, well, I mean, I'm just kinda starting...
-我听说你也要加入了  -对
- I hear you're coming in. - Yeah.
没错 你紧盯目标
Yeah, eyes on the prize.
可我要紧盯你
Well, I have got my eye on you.
如果你需要任何帮助
You need any help,
我说真的 任何帮助 或需要建议
seriously, any help, any advice, just, you know,
都他妈咽肚子里 好吗
don't fuckin' bother, OK?
我逗你的 表弟
I'm only razzing you, cuz.
你还迷糊呢
You're dreaming, really.
我就是逗你玩
I'm razzing you.
-好吧  -就是个玩笑
- OK. - That was a joke.
不 我说真的
No, really.
你知道吗 我可能看上去挺逗的
You know, the thing, I may look really fun,
-知道吗  -知道
- you know? - Yeah.
但你要知道
But the thing about me
我就是个彻头彻尾的混蛋
is that I'm a terrible, terrible prick.
你又上当了 我又骗到你了
I got you again. I just got you again.
太逗了老兄 看你表情
Fuck me, man, your face.
我们是哥们
Pals. Yes?
好吧
Yeah.
你能亲我吗
Would you kiss me?
-什么 亲你  -你能吗
- What? Kiss you? - Would you?
我要是让你亲呢
If I asked you to?
-我会亲你吗  -如果我命令你亲 你亲吗
- Would I kiss you? - If I told you to? Huh?
-我不...  -得了
- I don't...  - Come on.
我开玩笑的 开个玩笑
I'm joking. I'm joking.
-好了 西沃恩 -开打吧
- All right, Siobhan. - Bring it!
挥棒
Batter swing!
就是这样
Just like that!
等下 等一会 等等 抱歉
Hold up. Hang on, hang on. Sorry.
-抱歉  -嘘 嘘
- Apologies. - Boo! Boo.
亲爱的 嘘他
Honey, boo him.
-不好意思 我得走了  -你真没劲
- Yeah. OK. Sorry. I gotta run. - Boo!
要摊牌了
It's the crunch.
弗兰克 你来主持一下
Frank, will you be link man here?
爸
Dad?
去吧
Of course.
来这儿 宝贝
Come here, sweetie.
如果他要走 公平起见 我们队还需要一个人
Well, if Kendall's going, we need one more to make it fair!
坚持住 击球手
Keep it up, slugger.
那边的小孩 看这里
The kid. Hey! Hello!
对 就是你
Hello! Kid. Yeah. Yes.
你想加入吗
You. You. You wanna play?
孩他爸 他能上场吗
Dad, can he play?
当然 去吧
Yes. Sure.
谢了 孩他爸
Thank you, Dad.
是我 怎么样
Yeah, hey, what's up?
我听说你正准备一篇报道
I just got some background
我入手了一些背景资料
for the story I heard you had cookin'.
对 我认识肯德尔·罗伊
That's right. Yeah, I know Kendall Roy.
他说洛根已经没救了
And he's saying Logan's lost it.
就是这样
Yeah, that's right.
某些董事成员和高层管理人员
Some board members and senior management,
想让他走人
they want him out.
我听和家族走得很近的人说的
That's what I'm hearing from people close to the family.
那群墙头草
Those disloyal fucks.
就是... 和家族走得近的线人
Just... Just say source close to the family.
-高了  -太高了
- That's high. - Too high.
你搞得定的 放轻松 别紧张
You're gonna be fine. Relax, don't worry about it.
-你能打中球吗  -能
- Can you hit a ball? - Yeah.
很好 因为如果你
Great, because I will give you
打出了全垒打 我就给你一百万美金
one million dollars if you hit a home run.
-我没开玩笑 好吗  -真的吗
- I'm dead serious, OK? - For real?
千真万确 一百万美金
Yes, for real. A million dollars.
亲爱的 你的... 包呢
Honey, where's the... your bag?
我也想挣一百万 把球棒给我
Hey, I'll do it for a million. Give me that.
开玩笑的 你加油
Just kidding. You're good.
好了
All right.
我不懂你笑什么 我可是非常严肃的
I don't know why you're smiling. I am dead serious.
我会给你一百万现金
I will give you one million dollars, cash,
如果你他妈能打出全垒打
for a home fucking run.
小罗 别犯贱
Rome, don't be an asshole.
我没犯贱 我要给他点物质刺激
I'm not being an asshole. I want him incentivized.
多有趣
This is fun.
这只是个游戏 天 你别这么认真
It's a game. Jeez, stop being so serious.
看到了吗
Huh?
证人们
Witnesses.
祝你好运 我相信你能行
Good luck. I believe in you.
好了 来吧
All right, let's do this!
一百万美金
One million dollars.
来吧
OK, come on.
-打中了  -孩子 快跑
- That's it. - Run, kid!
-打中了  -飞得真远
- That's a hit. - That's a damn hit.
快 小西 我在这
Come on, Shiv! I'm here, Shiv!
-快  -汤姆
- Come on! - Tom!
快 快 再跑快点
Come on! Come on, run faster!
-不  -孩子 运气不好
- No! No! - Bad luck, kid.
你就差那么一点点
Oh, no! You were so damn close!
就那么一点点
That was so close!
天啊
Oh, my goodness!
真可怜 但不好意思
Oh, that is so sad! Oh, I'm sorry.
钱不能给你了 顺便说句 钱差点就是你的了
I can't give it to you. That would have counted, by the way.
如果你刚跑完了 就真的是全垒打了
That was almost a home run, if you went all the way around.
不过你真的努力了
But it was a really good effort.
真的 很精彩
Really. Quite tremendous.
拿着这个 回到你的生活
So take this back to your life.
这是一百万的四分之一 好好享受
It's a quarter million. Enjoy.
孩子... 打得很棒
Son... magnificent effort.
-谢谢  -很棒
- Thank you. - Magnificent.
-来这里  -没关系的
- Come here. - It's OK.
劳伦斯
Hey, Lawrence.
真可惜那个提案失败了
Sorry the other offer fell through.
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know what happened.
不过待宰的羊已经养肥了 是吧
But we fattened the goose nice now, right?
我给你1.4亿
The number is 140.
现金 股票也可以
Cash, with a stock alternative.
你加入我们
You're on our board.
股票到手 你会分到一份不错的羹
Take the stock, you'll own a nice piece of us.
好吧 这提议很诱人
Well, that is an appealing package.
你说得没错 是很诱人
It is, yeah. It's appealing.
但你最好想清楚 因为我代表整个公司
You better play nice, though. Because I'm the whole company.
当然 我觉得你不会走的
Yeah, I think you're gonna stick around
因为我会在你嘴里塞满了钱
because I'm gonna stuff your mouth with so much money
你拉屎都拉的小金人
you're gonna shit gold figurines.
保密协议 无表决权股票 竞业禁止
Non-disclosure agreement. Non-voting shares. Non-compete.
你会被我关进金笼子 屁眼里插满银阴茎
I'm going to lock you in a golden cage, fuck you with a silver dildo,
收着我的钱 唱我想听的歌
and pay you so much you sing whatever song I want.
-别急 你还需要我的推荐  -不 我不需要
- Easy. You still need me to recommend this. - No, I don't.
因为我的提案太他妈好了 你不得不接受
This is a deal so fucking good you have to take it,
否则我们法庭见
or we'll see you in court.
哥们
Dude.
你还好吗 先生 事情还顺利吗
How you doing, sir? How's everything?
我叫科林 我为洛根·罗伊先生和他的家族工作
I'm Colin. I work for Mr. Logan Roy and the Roy family.
我们希望您能对今天的事保密
We'd like to keep this quiet today, if you'll agree to that.
我们希望和您签订一份保密协议
We'd like to have you sign a non-disclosure agreement.
-你想再干五年吗  -对 弗兰克
- You wanted five? - Oh, Frank. Yeah.
我一直在想
I've been thinking
现在 是不是该给你分配新职位
if now isn't a time for a new role for you.
好吧 什么职位
OK. As in what sort?
轻松点的
Light duties.
轻松的
你耍我吗 洛根 开我
Are you kidding me? Logan. Me?
你手机应该收到了一封任命信
There should be a press release on your phone.
看看吧
Proof it.
你可能想再润色下 写得挺直白的
You might want to give it a bit of color, it's quite dry.
就这样吗 这样对我 都过了30...
That's it? To me. That's it? After 30...
老天 就在这林子里
Jesus Christ. Here?
你是你的所为 洛根 你知道吗
You are what you do, Logan. You know that?
最终 你只不过是你的所为
In the end, you're just what you do.
别担心 你会拿到补贴
Don't worry, you'll get your nut.
康纳
Connor!
小西 罗曼
Shiv! Roman!
坐那架直升机
The other helicopter.
科林 交给你了
Colin, see to it.
截止日期已经正式过了
Well, officially the deadline has passed.
所以... 你们怎么想
So... what do you say, kids?
弗兰克什么情况
What's the Frank situation?
弗兰克与我们无关了
Frank's out of the picture.
怎么
Yeah?
他出局了 由汤姆接替
Frank's dead. Tom's stepping up,
小西也在考虑一个新职位
and Shiv's thinking about a new role.
所以 都满意了吗
So, are we good?
小西觉得呢
Um... Shiv?
小罗
Rome?
康纳
Con?
我听他俩的 他们说了算
I'm with these two. What they say goes.
我们认为这对我们没什么用
Our position is this doesn't quite work for us.
就目前来说
At present.
你说啥
You what?
作为一个提议来说 还不够吸引人
It's not sufficiently attractive as a proposition.
你们他妈扯淡呢
Are you fuckin' joking?
我们懂的 真的
We get that. We do.
而且我们也很乐意帮忙 尤其我
And we would love to help. I would love to help.
那帮啊
Then help.
但我们连权力都失去了 为什么还要帮你
But why would I when I'm giving away power?
有什么理由这么做
Why would I do that?
-那...让凯莉  -凯莉是谁
- So... so Kelly, uh... - Who's Kelly?
让凯莉准备一些数据
Kelly will set up some figures.
-他应该看到...  -爸
- He should see that, uh... - Dad?
-爸  -对 他...
- Dad? - Yeah, he...
爸 这只是初始意愿 爸
Dad, it's just a first position. Dad?
能领会... 那个...
Get a grasp of what... what...
-爸 爸  -爸
- Dad! Dad! - Dad!
爸
Dad!
-爸 爸  -爸
- Dad! Dad! - Dad! Dad!
去医院 把我们送到医院
Just, yeah. A hospital. Take us to a hospital.
马上
OK, yeah, now!
他昏过去了吗
Has he fainted?
-他昏过去了 他身上好烫  -真的很烫 怎么回事
- He fainted? He's hot. - He's really hot. I don't know.
-肯德尔  -怎么了
- Kendall? - Yeah.
你听说那消息了吗
Have you heard the news?
什么
What?
成交
Deal.
太让人兴奋了 我很期待...
It's all very exciting. I can't wait to...
-我们成交了吗  -是的
- We got a deal? - Yeah.
-说真的  -真的
- Serious? - Yes?
哥们
Oh, dude.
听着 我觉得...
Listen, I think...
你做了非常明智的决定
I think you've made a really great decision
我希望你不要介意我刚说的那些话
and I hope there's no hard feelings over all the shit-talking.
不会 没关系
Oh, no, no, it's cool.
没事的
It's cool.
我刚说的消息是
So, the news I was talking about
你父亲刚突发脑溢血
is that your dad just had a brain hemorrhage.
什么
What?
是的 我很抱歉
Yeah. I'm so sorry.
-你...  -但...
- Are you... - But...
你就在刚才引狼入室
you just invited me into the chicken coop.
没有你老爸来保护你
And without Daddy around to protect you,
我会把你们所有人吃干抹净
I'm gonna eat you all.
一个接着一个
One by fucking one.
喂
Hello?
肯德尔 你终于接了
Kendall. Thank God.
我们一直在联系你...
We've been trying to reach you. Um...
爸进医院了
Dad is in the hospital.
他...
He's...
我们刚在直升机里 很快到了医院
We were in the helicopter, and we got here really fast,
但他们认为...
but they think...
还不确定 但医生认为他突发了脑溢血
We don't know. They think he's had a brain hemorrhage.
如果你能现在赶过来
If you could get here really soon,
那就太好了
that'd be good.
对不起
I'm sorry.
多数首次购房买家选择新港海滩
Most first-time homebuyers would love to live in Newport Beach.
但新港海滩的均价超过一百万美金
But average home price in Newport Beach is over $1 million.
所以 大多数房产...
So, most of the homes...
出现了一定幅度的股票波动
There is a degree of stock market volatility
据说韦斯达·罗伊科的总裁已病危
As Waystar Royco's chairman is reported to be in critical condition
接下来报道一起重大医疗事故...
following a major medical incident...